



ALEJANDRO MARTÍN

3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR

- alehamartinva@gmail.com
- +34 671 213 938
- https://alehaaaa.github.io/
- Berlin, Germany Barcelona, Spain

PROFILE

I am a 3D character animator with intuition and an eye for detail. Experienced in production environments, receiving feedback from the Animation Director and Supervisor and collaborating with other Animators and the Rigging team, always pursuing a more efficient pipeline with custom scripts and tools.

I am excited to contribute to a production to grow with the team.

EDUCATION

EXPERIENCE

MASTER IN 3D CHARACTER ANIMATION

ECIB | 2021 - 2022

Lip-sync · Advanced Acting

DEGREE IN ANIMATION

ECIB | 2019 - 2021

2D · StopMotion · 3D

ACTING INTRODUCTION

EÒLIA THEATER SCHOOL 2021 - 2022

Learnt to embrace a character

SKILLS

M AUTODESK MAYA



A ADOBE SUITE

BLENDER

English (C1, Advanced)
Spanish (Native)
Catalan (Native)

JUNIOR 3D ANIMATOR - DIE SCHULE DER MAGISCHEN TIERE 3 LUMATIC (BERLIN, GERMANY) | NOV 2023 - MAY 2024

Brought ideas in and, through collaborative teamwork, enhanced the animation with pipeline improvements and the development of tools.

- Animated a variety of animal characters, following references and learning about their anatomical behaviour.
- Specialized in animating lipsyncs in German dialogues.
- Received feedback directly from the Animation Director.
- Teamworked to puch sequences to their best acting potential.
- Improved the animation pipeline with custom tools and scripts.

3D CHARACTER ANIMATOR FOR SHORT FILM - EL MEGA ROBO ECIB (CINEMA SCHOOL OF BARCELONA) | OCT 2022 - SEP 2023

Collaboration with the Director and animators, creating the story from the ground up all together.

- Animated and developed character traits, maintaining personalities throughout the story, with the tight guidance of the Supervisor.
- Recorded multiple references, based on the time frame and dialogs.
- Worked on a pose Library whilst animating to test the characters.
- Implemented a production pipeline to organize shots and files, created a variety of tools to streamline the animation process.
- Keeping deliveries according to the established production timeline, always open-minded to changes.